https://jnwhiteusa.com/privacy-policy/

AboutProducts
Membrane SwitchesComplex User InterfacesGraphic OverlaysCustom LabelsCustom DecalsGaskets & LensesBacklightingElectrostatic Discharge (ESD) Shielding
Services
Manufacturing EngineeringDesign and DevelopmentRapid PrototypingAssemblyMembrane Switch TestingVendor Managed Inventory
Case StudiesResourcesBlogRequest a Quote
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for https://jnwhiteusa.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1 (800) 227-5718 or kboss@jnwhiteusa.com.
Also of Interestmembrane switch resistanceswitch manufacturersesd shielding
Support
Request a Quote
Send File
Careers
Products
Membrane Switches
Complex User Interfaces
Graphic Overlays
129 N Center St.Perry, NY 14530
JN White and Precision Answers are registered trademarks of J.N. White Associates, Inc. © 2020 JN White®. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
Questions? 1 (800) 227-5718
JN White is an ISO 9001:2015 and ITAR-certified manufacturer of membrane switches, graphic overlays, and custom labels.
All of our products are Made In The U.S.A. We specialize in the design and manufacture of complex graphic overlays, complex membrane switch keyboards, assembly and membrane switch testing. Our supporting products and services include: rapid prototyping; electronic shielding (ESD); backlighting (including addressable LEDs); design & development; vendor managed inventory (VMI); and medical device, UDI and UL label constructions. JN White works with global brands in the aerospace, medical device, medical instruments, industrial electronics, consumer appliance and defense (or military/DoD) industries. Made in America. Made in the U.S.
